# KALEB JENSEN

## FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

208.521.1307

✓ kalebcj@gmail.com

Q Lehi, Utah

linkedin.com/in/kalebjensen/

## WHY ME?

With 5+ years of customer-facing experience, including within SaaS, I am adept at running successful sales cycles. I'm now pursuing the next phase in my career as I have expanded my technical skills in Frontend Software Development focusing on JavaScript and React. Being self-taught, my ability to learn quickly and adapt make up for any gaps in my experience. Driven to grow, I'm eager to bring my skills to the right team.

# SKILLS

- React
- Next.js
- Git/Github
- TailwindCSS
- MaterialUI
- HTML /CSS /JavaScript
- UX/UI Design
- · Graphic Design
- Responsive Web Design

## TOOLS

- VSCode
- Figma
- Adobe Illustrator, Premiere, etc.
- Asana
- Shopify

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELORS
BUSINESS MANAGEMENT
Brigham Young University
April 2016

## CERTIFICATIONS

GOOGLE UX DESIGN
PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE
September 2022

## EXPERIENCE

#### **ACCOUNT MANAGER**

Gresham & Myers

2020 - Present

- Developed and executed strategy to create relationships with vendors and retailers resulting in \$50K+ new ARR
- Implemented QBR process focused on upselling, cross-selling, and renewals leading to a renewal rate of 90%+ each year
- Managed and prioritized multiple projects and accounts simultaneously, ensuring timely and successful delivery of services
- Coordinated multiple teams in design of a new customer-facing brand including logo, product, etc.

#### SALES AND MARKETING OPERATIONS MANAGER

The Domani Group

2020

- Created 15+ unique B2B email campaigns using Salesforce and Marketo resulting in 10% of Sales Revenue in Q2
- Analyzed data and created reporting to identify trends and relationships between Marketing and Sales
- Documented processes and requirements for A/B testing Marketing Strategies

## **ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE**

BambooHR

2019 - 2020

 Achieved ramping quota in three consecutive months as part of a leading team in the Sales organization

### **ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE**

Xvoyant

2018 - 2019

- Generated over \$100K in Sales owning entire Sale from "Prospecting" to "Close"
- Developed entire Sales Process for SMB/Mid-Market Sales, including outreach
- Implemented LinkedIn Sales Navigator, Outreach, Chorus, and trained others on software